오, 맙소사
Oh, my God.
새라? 문 잠겨있어
Sara? The door is locked.
잠깐만
Uh, just one second.
안녕
Hey.
무슨 일이야?
떠나는거야?
What's going on?
Are you leaving?
아파트 수리가 웬만큼 돼서
돌아가 보려고 해
The renovations on my apartment
are far enough along
that I can move back in.
지금 바로 가봐야
된다는 의미는 아니잖아
Doesn't mean you have to
head out right this second.
닐
Neal.
나 갈께
끝났어
I'm leaving.
Done.
몇 시간 전만 해도
우리 괜찮았잖아
A few hours ago, we were fine.
이젠 그냥 간다고?
무슨 일이 있었던거야?
Now you're walking out?
What happened?
글쎄, 언제든지 예상할 수
있는 일이었어, 닐
Well, the inevitable
happened, Neal.
내 말은, 우리 사이가 지속될꺼란
생각은 하지 않았잖아
I mean, we didn't think
this was gonna last.
그걸 기정사실로
정해놓은 줄은 몰랐는데
I didn't know
we were a fait accompli.
왜 그래
Come on.
재밌긴 하지만..
This was fun...
하지만 우리 둘은
정말 다른 사람이야
But we're
two very different people.
왜 그래, 새라
내가 누군지 항상 알고있었잖아
Oh, come on, Sara,
you've always known who I am.
그래, 네 말이 맞아
Yeah, you're right.
그래
Okay.
내가 말하려던게 어떤건지
알아냈나보네
I guess you figured out
everything I have to offer.
잘 될수도 있어
We could be good together.
알아
I know.
닐, 넌 구름속에서 살고있어..
Neal, you live in the clouds...
난 웨스트가 69번지에 살고있고..
And I live on West 69th.
난 아무것도 장담 못하겠지
I never promised you
anything else.
그렇겠지
I know.
그럼, 서로 갈 길을 가야겠네
Well, you found your way out.
나중에 나머지 것들을 가지러올게
I'll figure out
the rest of my things.
그래
Yeah.
카프리, 제발 몸 조심하구..
Caffrey, please take care
of yourself.
그리고 떠나갔다.
그냥 그렇게?
She walked out,
just like that?
그냥 그렇게요
Just like that.
그거.. 서로 결정한거야?
Was it, uh... mutual?
아뇨
No.
뭐라고 했는데?
What did she say?
우리는 다른 사람이라고 했어요
That we're different people.
물론, 넌 다르지
Well, of course
you're different.
다르다는게 인생을 흥미롭게 해주잖아
That's what makes
life interesting.
- 그 다음엔?
- 아무것도 없었어요
What's next?
Nothing.
아무것도?
Nothing?
그냥 가게 나뒀단 말야?
Just let her go?
우리가 불행했던건 아니에요.
아시죠?
It's not like we were
star-crossed, all right?
- 그냥 끝난것 뿐이에요
- 영원히?
It's over.
For good?
결국 잘한 일일거에요
For the best.
그래, 좋을대로 해
Okay, whatever you say.
좋은 아침
Morning, sunshines.
용의자의 움직임은?
Any movement from our suspect?
두 번, 개와 산책했습니다
Walked his dog twice.
무슨 냄새죠?
What's that smell?
참치 샌드위치
Tuna sandwich.
- 반 남았어
- 괜찮아요
This half is up for grabs.
Pass.
카프리는 왜 데리고 오셨어요?
Why'd you bring Caffrey?
전문지식이 필요하기도 하고
I brought him for his expertise
여자친구 일도 있고 해서말야
and his company.
- 이렇게 놀리는걸 좋아하신다니까
- 그렇지
He likes to poke me with sticks.
I do.
나가보는게 어때?
Hey, why don't you head out?
내가 요원님이랑
같이 있을게
I can catch up Peter.
- 정말이야?
- 그래
You sure?
Yeah.
밴 밖으로 나가고 싶어
죽을만큼 안달난것 처럼 보이는데
You've got that look,
like you're dying
to get out of the van.
짐작도 못할걸
You have no idea.
- 천만에
- 고마워
You're welcome.
Thank you.
움직이지마!
손을 볼수 있도록 들어!
Freeze!
Hands where I can see them!
무기를 버리고
차서 내게 보내
당장!
Now!
조심히, 조심히
Easy, easy.
천천히, 천천히, 천천히
Slowly, slowly, slowly.
마스크를 벗어
Take off your mask.
이봐, 난 문제를 일으키고 싶지 않아
Look, I don't want any trouble.
Ugh!
청소하는걸 잊었거나
큰 싸움이 있었나보네요
Either you forgot
to clean up for company,
or that was quite a fight.
맞아
Tell me about it.
칼리를 훈련한 녀석이었어
(Kali : 필리핀 실전 무슬)
Guy was trained in Kali.
틀림없이 전문가야
Definitely a professional.
겨우 총을 쏴서
오른쪽 어깨를 맞췄어
I was able to get a shot off
that hit him
in the right shoulder.
공격한 놈이 꽤 용의주도한데
Your attacker's a ghost.
뉴욕경찰이 순찰차와 헬리콥터로
지역을 검색 중이야
NYPD's got cruisers and choppers
searching the area.
아무 증거도 없어
No trace.
- 그가 뭘 쫓았나요?
- 이거
What was he after?
That.
아파트에 침입해서
그림엽서를 훔쳤다?
Guy breaks into an apartment
to steal a postcard?
짐미가 네 친구야?
Jimmy a friend of yours?
네, 짐미 윌슨. 아나폴리스의 오랜 친구에요
(Annapolis : 미 해군 사관학교 소재지)
Yeah, Jimmy Wilson.
Old buddy from Annapolis.
수수께끼의 그림엽서는
오랜 친구에게 문제가 발생했다는거죠
Cryptic postcards
from old friends mean trouble.
제 경험에 의하면요
In my experience.
마지막으로 들은건, 배럿-듄
보안회사에서 일하고 있다는 것이야
Last I heard, he worked
for Barrett-Dunne security.
- 사유 군대를 대여해주는 곳이요?
- 맞아
Private military for hire?
Yeah.
남아공의 프레토리아에서 소인이 찍혔어
(Pretoria : 남아공 행정수도)
It's postmarked
Pretoria, South Africa.
- 집에서는 아주 먼곳이네요
- 음
That's a long way from home.
Mm.
- 제가 좀?
- 그래
May I?
Yeah.
스탬프 아래에 뭔가 있네요
There's something
under the stamp.
- 핀셋이나 뭐..
- 옙
Do we have tweezers or...
Yep.
핀셋
Tweezers.
고마워요
Thank you.
Yeah.
- 마이크로닷이네요
- 구식이네
(microdot : 약 1mm 크기로 축소한 사진)
It's a microdot.
Old-school.
맞아요, 필름카메라와 가위만 있으면 되죠
Yeah, but all you need is a film
camera and a pair of scissors.
침입, 용병, 비밀메시지
Break-ins, mercenaries,
secret messages.
다른 날과 마찬가지죠?
Just another day, huh?
밴 밖의 삶에 오신걸 환영합니다
Welcome to life
outside the van.
영어자막 : www.addic7ed.com (honeybunny)
한글자막 : EzLoves
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
블로그 : vstu77.blog.me
오타, 오역 등 피드백 남겨주세요!
WHITECOLLAR
S03E08 As You Were
ORIGINAL DATE 2011/07/26
CREATED BY
JEFF EASTIN
좋은 소식이긴 한데
Great news.
전혀 도움이 안되네요
You've been no help at all.
몇 분 이내로 가겠습니다
I'll be up in a few minutes.
연구소에서 마이크로닷의
사진 확대를 끝냈어
Lab's finished
enhancing the microdot.
보내올거야
They're sending it over.
배럿-듄에서 짐미가
일한다는걸 확인했는데
Barrett-Dunne confirmed
Jimmy's an employee
그의 지위나 역할에 대해선
말해주지 않았습니다
but won't say where he's
stationed or in what capacity.
네
All right.
이 민간 용병팀에 대해서
뭘 더 알고있죠?
What else do we know about this
private-mercenary outfit?
유튜브의 고양이 비디오 같은
쓰레기를 만들어내고 있어
They make Blackwater
look like a YouTube cat video.
사기꾼 제거, 암살 등과 연관되어있어
They've been linked with
rogue kill teams, death squads.
즐거움이 가득찬 집단처럼 들리네요
Sounds like
a fun group of guys.
말도 안됩니다
Doesn't make any sense.
짐미는 착한녀석이에요
Jimmy's one of the good guys.
둘이 무슨 관계였어?
What's the story
with the two of you?
학교에서 만났죠
Oh, we met at the Academy.
제겐 형제같은 사람이에요
He was like a brother to me.
5년동안 말안한 형제?
A brother you haven't talked to
in five years?
음, 우리는 같이 근무했죠
Well, we served our tours
together.
그는 군대에 남았고
전 하버드 법대에 갔었죠
He stayed in the military.
I went on to Harvard Law.
그래, 어쨌든 그의 부인이 문제의
해결책을 찾으려고 하는거구만
Well, whatever trouble he's in,
maybe his wife
can shed some light.
이자벨? 여기 왔어요?
Isabelle?
She's here?
그래. 아침에 왔어
Yeah.
She came in this morning.
윗층에서 다이애나에게 진술하고있어
She's upstairs,
giving Diana a statement.
혹시 문제가 되나?
That a problem?
아니요, 아닙니다
No, no.
전혀 문제되지 않아요
No problem at all.
요원님
Peter.
이자벨 윌슨씨입니다
This is Isabelle Wilson.
이자벨
Isabelle.
안녕
Hi.
음.. 만나서..
만나서 반가워
It's, uh...it's good --
it's good to see you.
그래, 만나서 반가워
Yeah, you too.
Uh...
그럼, 음
짐미에 대한건?
Uh, so, um,
anything from Jimmy?
알고있는 모든걸
베리건 요원에게 말했어
I told agent Berrigan
everything I know.
그리고 그가 괜찮은걸로 판명되면
죽여버릴꺼야
And if it turns out he's fine,
I'm gonna kill him.
어떻게 만나셨나요?
I take it you two have met.
CJ 와 저는 거의 결혼할 뻔 했죠
C.J. and I were a little bit
almost married once.
그건 마치..
It's kind of a...
긴 이야기군요
Long story.
방금 존스를 CJ 라고 부른거에요?
Did she just call him
C.J.?
- 으흠
- 아지벨, 이쪽은, 음..
Mm-hmm.
Isabelle, this is, uh...
- 피터 버크 요원입니다
- 피터 버크 요원
Agent Peter Burke.
Peter Burke, yes,
그리고, 이쪽은 닐 카프리
and, uh, Neal Caffrey.
안녕하세요.
버크요원의 컨설턴트(CI)입니다
Hi. Agent Burke, C.I.,
CJ 와 헷갈려하진 마세요
not to be confused
with his C.J.
무시하세요
No.
Ignore him.
와주셔서 감사합니다.
Thank you for coming in,
Ms. Wilson.
문제없습니다
No problem.
그럼, 데려다 줄게
괜찮지?
So, uh,
I'll walk you out, okay?
만나서 반가웠습니다
Nice to meet you.
너 좀 봐
Look at you.
법학 학위에, FBI 요원이라니
Law degree, FBI agent.
넌 항상 진취적이었지
You always were
an over-achiever.
넌
And you.
프린스턴대 언어학 교수잖아
Linguistics professor
at Princeton.
좀 찾아봤을지도
I may have looked you up.
멋져 보여
You look good.
너도 나쁘지 않아 보여
You're not looking so bad
yourself.
들어봐, 짐미가 곤경에 처했다면
우리가 해결해야 해
Listen, if, uh, Jimmy's
in trouble, we'll sort it out.
그렇지 않길 바라야지
Let's just hope he isn't.
두달 전, 배럿-듄은 짐미를
팔라듐 광산의 보안을 강화하기위해
Two months ago,
Barrett-Dunne dispatched Jimmy
to shore up security
at a palladium mine
남아공의 프레토리아로 파견하였습니다
- 닐?
they own and operate in Pretoria,
South Africa. Neal?
전 그 광산은 들어본적이 없는데요
I've never been near that mine.
- 아니, 팔라듐에 대한 전문지식을 말해봐
- 네, 물론이죠
No, could you highlight
the finer points
of palladium, please?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
팔라듐은 전화기, 컴퓨터, 자동차 부품에 쓰이죠
Palladium is used in cellphones,
computers, auto parts.
은보다 20배의 가치가 있고
런던극장의 이름으로도 손색 없습니다
It's also 20 times
the value of silver
and not a bad name
for a London theater.
짐미는 그곳에 보내졌고
Jimmy was sent there
이자벨은 '스트라이커'라고 불리는
사람이 있다고 했어
by a man known to Isabelle
as Striker.
그를 잠시 한번 만났지만
진짜 이름을 알아내진 못했답니다
She met him once, briefly,
but didn't get his real name.
보아하니, 스트라이커는 인도와 중국과의
보안 계약에 대해 떠벌리고 다녔어
Apparently this Striker
was bragging
about securing contracts
in India and China.
배럿-듄 직원들의
정보와 사진을 요청한 상태이다
We've requested Barrett-Dunne’s
employee files and photos.
하지만 협조하고 있지 않죠
놀랍죠, 놀라워요
But they're not cooperating --
Surprise, surprise.
이자벨은 스트라이커와의 마지막 대화에서
In Isabelle's
last conversation with him,
짐미는 회사가 그를 가까이서
관찰하고 있다고 했어요
Jimmy believed the company
was keeping a close watch.
개인 전화와, 발신 우편물을
감시하고 있었군요
Monitoring his personal calls,
his outgoing mail.
마이크로닷이 설명 되는군
Explains the microdot.
그게 유일하게 정보를
보낼 수 있는 방법이였어
That was the only way he had
to get information out.
마이크로닷에 대해 얘기해보자
존스?
Speaking of microdots --
Jones?
이게 우리쪽 기술자가 뽑아낸 것입니다
This is
what our technicians extracted.
- 팔라듐 광산의 도식도네요
- 맞아
- It's a schematic of the palladium mine.
- Yep.
그리고 이건 광산자원부에서 6일전에
제출한 같은 광산의 도식도입니다
And this is a schematic
of the same mine
filed with the Department
of Mineral Resources
six days ago.
다른점이 있나?
Notice anything different?
공식 지도에는 표시되지 않은
별관이 있습니다
There's an entire annex
that isn't on the official map.
짐미가 저길 가리키고 있었다면..
If Jimmy's
pointing us there...
스트라이커일수 있는
배럿-듄의 누군가가
Then someone at Barrett-Dunne,
possibly Striker,
그를 멈추려고 애를
쓰고 있는것 같아
is going to great lengths
to stop him.
짐미를 찾을수 있는 최고의 기회는
Our best chance
at finding Jimmy
스트라이커가 관계된걸
알아내는 것이네요
is to figure out
what Striker's up to.
광산쪽을 자세히 살펴볼
팀을 만들어
I want a team
looking into the mine.
존스, 배럿-듄에 대해서 더 캐내봐
Jones, dig up what we can
on Barrett-Dunne.
필요할테니까
We need an in.
- 저는 뭐 할까요?
- 가까이 있어
Anything I can do?
Stay close.
무슨 일이에요?
What's going on?
우리의 인내가 결실을
내기 시작한것 같아
Our patience may have paid off.
DC 미술범죄국이 새로운 세잔 작품을 찾아냈어
(Cezanne : 프랑스 후기 인상파 화가)
D.C. Art Crimes
uncovered a new Cezanne
발티모어의 저장금고에서 말야
in a Baltimore storage vault.
유보트에서 나온 목록과 일치하나요?
Does it match either of the
Cezannes on the u-boat manifest?
아직 말은 없어
No word yet.
어느 쪽이든
내가 확인해 보고 싶어
Either way,
I want to see it myself.
크라머가 사진을 보낼꺼야
Kramer is sending over photos.
처음으로 목록에 있을
가능성이 있는거네요
This is our first potential hit off the list.
Mm.
충분히 기다리면
도둑은 실수를 하기 마련이지
If you wait long enough,
your thief will make a mistake.
별 문제 없지?
Everything okay?
- 네
- 가까이 있을게요
Yeah.
Staying close.
- 좋아
- 네
Good.
All right.
도움이 될지 모르겠지만
새라 일은 유감이야
For what it's worth,
I'm really sorry about Sara.
같이 있으면 꽤 즐거웠는데
(joie de vivre : 삶의 기쁨)
She has
an infectious joie de vivre.
정장도 멋지게 어울렸고 말이야
And she looks terrific
in pant suits.
내 장례식에서는
말하지 않겠다고 약속해줘
Promise me you'll never speak
at my funeral.
결국엔 그녀와의 연결고리를 끊어야 해
You were gonna have to cut ties
with her eventually.
시간이 얼마 남지 않았다고
Our days here are numbered.
FBI 에게 발각되지 않고
미술품을 팔려면 말야
Providing we find a way
to start selling off the art
without alerting the feds.
그래, 말나와서 말인데
요원님과 다이애나가 뭔가 꾸미고 있어
Yeah, speaking of, Peter
and Diana are up to something.
FBI? 뭔가 꾸미고 있다고?
Feds?
Up to something?
아이구 놀래라
Quelle surprise.
그래, 요즘에 둘이
밀실 회의를 많이 하더라고
Yeah, two closed-door meetings
in as many days?
대화를 찍어놨어
I videotaped
their conversation.
아, 대담한데
Ah, gutsy.
필사적이지, 뭐
Mm, well, desperate times.
무슨말 하는지 알겠어?
Can you tell
what they're saying?
오, 뭔가 "성공하다"
Oh,
something "paid off."
잠깐, 공무원씨가
"새로운 세잔"이래
Wait.
The Suit says, "new Cezanne."
확실해?
You sure?
아님 "루 맥클라나한" 일지도
Or possibly
"Rue McClanahan."
"새로운 세잔" 이 맞는거 같아
I'd go with "new Cezanne."
숨겨놓은 것 중에
세잔 작품이 한쌍 있잖아
We've got a pair of Cezannes
in our stash.
"연못위의 다리" 랑
"성 빅토리아의 산" 말이지?
"Bridge Over a Pond" and
"The Mount of Saint Victoria."
좋지않아, 모즈
Not good, Moz.
요원님이 아직도 유보트에서 나온
미술품들을 찾고 있는거야?
Peter's still looking into
the art from the u-boat?
맞아, 그는 포기할 사람이 아니지
Yeah, he's not one to give up.
수사권이 DC 미술범죄국으로
넘어갔다고 생각했었는데
I thought he handed
the investigation over
to D.C. Art Crimes.
부분적인 적하 목록은 넘겼지만
조사를 보고만 있진 않을꺼야
He may have handed over
the partial manifest,
but he wouldn't let go
of the investigation.
그가 신경쓰고 있는걸 알아내야겠네
Think you can find out
what he's up to?
내가 할 수 있는걸 해야지
I'll do what I can.
지난 주, 팔라듐 광산의 관리자가
지역 기자와 접선했습니다
Last week, the manager
of the palladium mine
reached out
to a local reporter.
어떤 불법적인 것이 진행되고 있어
말하고 싶다고 했더군요
She wanted to talk about something
illegal going on there.
그런데 말하기도 전에, 살해당했네요
Only before the manager
could talk, she was killed.
은폐의 냄새가 나는데요
Smells to me
like a cover-up.
존스, 짐미가 살인과 관계되었다면
Jones, if Jimmy's involved
in murder --
요원님, 그는 아니에요
Peter, he's not.
제 말은, 사실을 말하기위해
그림엽서를 보냈잖아요
I mean, he sent me that postcard
to expose the truth,
은폐되지 않게 말이죠
not to cover it up.
믿어주세요
Trust me,
짐미는 올바른 생각을 가졌어요
Jimmy is
on the right side of things.
확실하게 하려면 한가지 길 밖에 없네
Only one way to make sure.
스트라이커를 찾아야겠네요
We need to find
our elusive Striker.
우리가 생각하는 것 보다
찾기 쉬울지도 모르겠는데요
He may not be as elusive
as we thought.
이것 좀 보세요
Take a look at this.
배럿-듄의 연회가 내일 열리네요
Barrett-Dunne’s hosting
a reception tomorrow.
초대된 사람들만 올수있고
Open to invited guests
모두 현역이나 은퇴한 군인들이에요
and all active and retired
military personnel.
스트라이커가 참석할 가능성이 높아요
There's a good chance
Striker will be there.
좋아, 이자벨이 그를 봤으니
신분증을 만들어야겠어
Good. Isabelle's seen him,
so she can make the I.D.
군인 출신으로, 너도 가도 돼
And as former military,
you can go.
좋아요
Okay.
그럼, 제가 이자벨에게
연회에 참석하라고 말하길 바라시나요?
So, you, uh, you want me to ask
Isabelle to the reception?
만약..
If --
예전 관계가
문제가 되지 않는다면 말야
Unless it's a problem,
given your history with her.
좋아요, 들어보세요
O-okay, guys, look.
이자벨과 전 아나폴리스에서
작년에 만났어요
Isabelle and I met
my last year at Annapolis.
로스쿨을 같이 다녔지만
Stayed together
through law school.
난 FBI를 선택하고
그녀는 짐미를 선택했죠
I chose the FBI.
She chose Jimmy.
더 분명하게 해야할게 있나요?
아니, 괜찮아
Anything else we got to clear up?
No, I'm good, I'm good.
- 닐, 다이애나, 괜찮아?
- CJ 에 대해서요
Neal, Diana, you're good?
About C.J. --
특별한 별칭 같은 거였나요?
Is that a special pet name
only she calls you,
- 우리가 그렇게 불러도 되나요?
- 닐
or can we call you that?
Neal.
- 요원님이 괜찮냐고 하셔서..
- 그냥 해본 소리였어
You asked if I was good.
It was rhetorical.
물어보고 싶었어요
괜찮다고 하죠 뭐
I want to ask him. Okay, apparently, I'm good.
Shush.
닐도 괜찮대
다른 질문 없지?
He's good.
Any questions?
전혀, 전혀 없습니다
No, no, not at all.
위험한 녀석으로부터 보호하기 위해
전 약혼녀의 남편에 대한 팀을 꾸리는거
Teaming up
with my ex-fiancee
to confront a dangerous man
to find her missing husband --
재밌을것 같네요
Should be fun.
요원님, 들어왔습니다
Peter, I'm in.
좋아
Good.
이자벨을 관찰하고있어?
You have eyes on Isabelle?
이런 세상에나
Sweet lord almighty.
동의하는걸로 알겠어
I'll take that
as an affirmative.
네, 요원님
Yes, sir.
중위 존스라, 와우
Lieutenant Jones. Wow.
흰 옷을 입은건 본적이..
I haven't seen you
in dress whites since...
네 결혼식 이후로 없을거야
Your wedding.
정말 오랜만이야
It's been a while.
이렇게 하는거 괜찮아?
You okay doing this?
네가 괜찮으면, 나도 괜찮아
If you're okay, I'm okay.
그래, 난.. 난 괜찮아
Yeah, I'm -- I'm okay.
저기 오는 중령이..
The commander coming in --
그 사람이야
그가 스트라이커야
That's him.
That's Striker.
실례합니다
Excuse me.
저기 중령이 누군가요?
The commander --
Who is he?
헨리 밴 혼
배럿-듄의 최고 운영 책임자입니다
Henry van Horn,
C.O.O. of Barrett-Dunne.
고마워요
요원님, 들으셨죠?
Thank you.
Peter, you get that?
그래. 다이애나에게
찾아보라고 했어
Yeah.
I'm having Diana run the name.
목쪽에 상처가 몇개
있는 것 같아 보입니다
Looks like he has a couple of
bruises on his neck, as well.
너를 공격했던 사람이라고 생각하나?
You think he's the guy
who attacked you?
곧 알게 되지 않을까요
We're about to find out,
aren't we?
좋은 오후입니다, 중령님
Afternoon, commander.
중위
Lieutenant.
우리 본적있지 않나요?
Have we met?
아닌것 같은데
I don't believe we have.
아, 클린턴 존스
FBI 입니다
Ah, Clinton Jones, FBI.
어떠세요?
How you doing?
짐미 윌슨을 찾고있습니다
I'm looking for Jimmy Wilson.
전 어디있는지 모르겠는데, 당신은요?
Don't have any idea
where he is, do you?
부인에게 직접 물어보지 그래?
Why don't you ask his wife?
벌써 물어봤죠
He already did.
이자벨
Isabelle.
당신의 남편은 직책을 그만뒀습니다
Your husband
abandoned his post.
상황을 보아하니
And by the looks of things,
당신은 남편을 떠날 준비가
되어있진 않은것 같군요
you're not far off
from abandoning your husband.
짐미는 이유없이 사라지지 않아요
Jimmy wouldn't have disappeared
without a reason.
짐미는 이해할수 없는 행동을 하는
고약한 버릇이 있습니다
Jimmy has a nasty habit
of getting in over his head.
내가 틀렸다고 말해봐요
Tell me I'm wrong.
실례하겠습니다
If you'll excuse me.
뭐 좀 얻어냈나?
What'd you find out?
지미가 제게 큰 빚을
졌다는거 말고는 없습니다
Son of a bitch owes me
a flat-screen.
짐미인게 확실한가?
You're sure it was Jimmy?
그럼 찾아내
Then find him.
그녀석이 모든걸 날려버릴 수 있어
He could blow the whole thing.
무슨 일이야, 존스?
What's going on, Jones?
밴 혼이 서둘러 파티를 떠나려고합니다
Van Horn's leaving this party,
and fast.
짐미!
Jimmy!
FBI!
얘기좀 하시죠
We need to talk.
당신은 날 보호할 수 없소
You can't protect me.
그 누구도 말이오
No one can.
짐미
Jimmy, don't...
짐미, 가지마세요
가지마세요, 짐미!
Jimmy, don't run, don't run.
Jimmy!
짐미가 왜 도망갔어?
Why did Jimmy run?
제이슨 본 흉내 그만내고
(Jason Bourne : 영화 본 시리즈의 주인공)
If he turns himself in
돌아오면 안전할텐데
instead of pulling
a Jason Bourne, he'd be safe.
FBI 가 보호해 주잖아
The FBI
would have protected him.
이즈, 짐미는 그렇게 생각하지 않아
Izz, look,
Jimmy doesn't think so.
배럿-듄은 강력해
Barrett-Dunne is powerful.
돌아와서 그들이 하려하는 걸
노출하려고 했어
He came back to try to expose
what they're up to.
CJ..
C.J...
짐미는 네가 생각하는
그런 영웅이 아니야
Jimmy isn't the hero
you think he is.
밴 혼이 광산에서 뭘 꾸미든간에
짐미도 그 일부분이었어
Whatever van Horn is up to
in that mine, Jimmy is a part of.
적어도, 그랬어
At least, he was.
무슨 소릴 하는거야?
What are you talking about?
광산에서 돌아온 후로
After he got back to the mine,
돈을 송금하기 시작했어
많은 돈을 말야
he started sending cash --
a lot.
얼마나?
How much?
약 10만 달러 정도
Close to $100,000.
보너스 같은 거라고 말했어
He said
it was some kind of bonus.
이즈, 나랑 뭔가
Izz, you know,
this is something
이야기 하고 싶은것 같은데
that you might have wanted
to share with me.
나도 알아, 그를 지켜야
한다고 느꼈어
I know. I felt like
I had to protect him.
내 남편이잖아
He's my husband.
도대체 어떻게 이 회사와
연관 되어버린거야?
How the hell did he even get
involved with this company?
짐미니까
Because he's Jimmy.
항상 더 좋은 부양자가
되기 위해서 노력했지
He's always pushing to do more,
to be a better provider.
너와 비교하는걸 멈추지 않았어
He's never stopped
comparing himself to you.
나랑?
To me?
네가 기준이었어
You're the gold standard.
나?
Me?
너도 알다시피, 난 밴에서 일하고
계단 밑에서 살지
You know, I work in a van.
I live under the stairs.
- 난
- 넌 너무 겸손해
I --
You're way too modest.
좋든 실든간에
넌 좋은 사람이야, 클린턴 존스
Like it or not, you're
a good man, Clinton Jones.
드물 정도로 말야
That's kind of a rare thing.
- 저기, 요원님
- 그래
- Hey, boss.
- Hey.
세잔에 관한 좋은 소식과
나쁜 소식이 있습니다
So, good news, bad news
on the Cezanne.
좋은 소식부터 말해봐
Start with the good news.
DC 에서 1870년대에 만들어진
진품임을 확인했습니다
D.C. says
it's the genuine article.
Dates back to the 1870s.
- 하지만 이건 목록의 아홉번째껀 아니지
- 네
But it's not number 9 on the sub's manifest.
No.
아홉번째껀 "연못위의 다리" 입니다
Number 9 is listed
as "Bridge Over a Pond."
연못은 있는데 다리는 없네
Pond but no bridge.
그래서 나쁜 소식입니다
Hence the bad news.
만약, 그 모든게
What if, after all this...
돌아다니지 않는다면 말이지?
It's not out there?
사실..
Honestly...
안심될꺼야
I'd be relieved.
여기있던 파일 봤어요?
Hey, did you get those files?
그럼요, 다 가지고 있죠
Yeah, I got everything.
- 오
- 괜찮아요, 고마워요
Ooh.
I got it. Thanks.
고마워, 다이애나
Thanks, Diana.
소식이 있어
I got some news.
요원님이 DC 미술범죄국에
사진을 요청했어
Peter requested photos
from D.C. Art Crimes.
- 왜 그랬을까?
- 모즈..
Why would he do that?
Moz...
내 생각엔 요원님이 아직
유보트의 목록을 가지고 있을 것 같아
I think he still has
a copy of the u-boat manifest.
파라다이스로 가는 티켓 말이지
Our ticket to paradise.
FBI 사무실에 숨겨놨다고 생각해?
You think he'd keep it
at the FBI?
글쎄, 나를 의심한다고 하면..
Well, if he suspects me...
- 의심하고 있지
- 위험할꺼야
Which he does.
...It'd be risky.
하지만 가능성 있지?
But possible?
가능해
It's possible.
오늘 저녁에 둘러봐야겠어
I'll go back tonight
and look around.
수상쩍어 보이지 않을까?
Won't that look suspicious?
난 범죄자야
I'm a criminal.
불규칙한 생활을 하지
We keep odd hours.
아직 계시네요?
You still here?
짐미의 총알이
검사를 마치고 돌아왔어
Jimmy's bullet
came back from forensics.
뭐가 보이나?
What do you see?
놋쇠 케이스네요
별로 특별한건 없어요
Brass casing.
Nothing strange about that.
자세히 살펴봐
Look closer.
팔라듐으로 채워져있네요
It's filled with palladium.
바로 그거야
말이 안돼
Exactly.
Doesn't make sense.
들어봐
Walk through it with me.
네
All right.
밴 혼이 개인적으로 짐미를 광산으로 보냈고
Van Horn personally sends Jimmy
to the mine.
짐미는 뭔가 불법적인일에
관여되었죠
Jimmy gets involved
in something illegal there.
광산 관리자가 불어버리겠다고 하자
살해당했어
The manager of the mine says
she's gonna talk. She's killed.
짐미도 살해당하기 전에
빠져나오고 싶었겠죠
And now Jimmy wants out
because he didn't think
it would escalate to murder.
아니면 짐미가 살인과 관계있고
Or Jimmy's involved
in the murder,
죄가 있기 때문에
도망다니고 있을 수도 있어
and he ran because he's guilty.
항상 그렇게 의심하세요?
Do you always presume guilt?
죄를 진 사람은 죄를 저지르지
Guilty people do guilty things.
내가 틀렸나?
Am I wrong?
토론은 여기까지 하고
For the sake of argument,
제 생각을 말해볼게요
let's go with my version.
좋아
Fine.
짐미는 빠져나오고 싶어했고
Jimmy wants out.
Mm-hmm.
밴 혼은 짐미가 빠져
나가려는걸 알아차렸다
Van Horn realizes
Jimmy's thinking of leaving,
그래서 못나가게 했다
so he sits on him.
아마 전화를 감시하거나
Probably starts
monitoring his calls,
이메일을 확인하는것부터 시작했을거에요
checking his mail.
그때 짐미가 마이크로닷을
존스에게 보냈고
That's when Jimmy sends Jones
the microdot.
짐미는 비밀리에
그 지역으로 와서
Jimmy slips
back into the country...
저걸 놓고 갔지
And gives me that.
왜 팔라듐으로 총알을 만들었을까?
Why make a bullet
out of palladium?
최첨단 늑대인간?
High-tech werewolves?
장난치지 말고
Keep thinking.
밴 혼은 배럿-듄이
인도와 중국과의 계약이 있다고 했죠
Van Horn
said Barrett-Dunne
had contracts
in China and India.
팔라듐의 수요가 높은 나라지
Countries with a high demand
for palladium.
네, 하지만 팔라듐을 그 나라로
수입하는건 불법은 아니죠
Yeah, but it's not illegal
to import palladium
into those countries.
그래, 그렇지만 관세가 있잖아
No, but there are tariffs.
탈세야
It's a tax dodge.
살인, 침입, 가짜 총알
Murder, break-ins,
fake bullets,
겨우 세금 몇달러 아끼자고
이런짓을 했다구요?
all so our soldier of fortune
can save a few tax dollars?
연단위로 따지면 수천만 달러지
Oh, try tens of millions
every year.
와우
Wow.
제가 세금 안내는게 다행이군요
Glad I don't pay taxes.
음
Mm.
- 왜요?
- 우리 꽤 잘하고 있는데
What?
We're good at this.
우리가요
We are.
이젠 어쩌죠?
What now?
이제 밴 혼을 직접
만나야 할때가 된것 같아
I think it's time
van Horn and I
had a little face-to-face.
요원님
Peter...
밴 혼이 오고있습니다
Van Horn's on his way up.
좋아
Good.
아니요. 좋지 않습니다
No.
It's really not.
- 좋은 오후요, 요원들
- 봅시다
- Afternoon, agents.
- Let's see it.
국가 안전을 위하여
모든 배럿-듄의 인터뷰는
"In the interest
of national security,
"all Barrett-Dunne interviews
to be conducted by,
미국 연방 지방검찰청을
통하시길 바랍니다
and scheduled through,
the U.S. attorney's office."
위쪽에 있는 내 친구들이
좀 바쁘다는군요
My friends over there
say they're busy,
아마 내년 봄쯤은 되야
시작할 수 있을것 같군요
although they may be able to fit
you in sometime next spring.
법무부에 빽이 있어서
(DOJ : 법무부)
You got the D.O.J.
in your pocket.
꽤나 특별하다고 생각하나 본데?
You must think
you're pretty special, huh?
존스 요원
Agent Jones.
네 친구 부인이 너랑 있지 않아서
거의 못알아 볼 뻔 했네
I almost didn't recognize you
without your best friend's wife
on your arm.
여기서 끝나는건 아니야, 밴 혼
이렇게는 아니지
This doesn't end here, van Horn.
Not like this.
높은 곳에 네 빽들이 있다고?
나도 있어
You got friends in high places?
So do I.
그럼 제 변호사가
소식 전해주길 바라겠습니다
I almost considered
having my attorney
deliver the news for me.
그랬으면 좋겠지만요
Glad I didn't.
재밌었습니다
This was fun.
가자
Come on.
존스, 존스, 존스
Jones. Jones, Jones.
앞으로 어떻게 할건지 알려줄까?
You know what kind of fun
we're gonna have?
짐미를 찾고
널 쓰려트려 주지
We're gonna find Jimmy,
and then we're gonna
take you down.
음. 향수 적게 쓰는게 좋을거 같은데
Hmm. I'd suggest
using less cologne.
짐미가 돌아왔을때
You wouldn't want Jimmy
smelling you on his wife
자기 부인한테서 네 향수 냄새가
나는걸 알아차리면 안될테니까
when he gets back.
진정해
Hey. Easy.
진정해, 진정해
그냥 가게 나둬
Let him go. Come on. Come on!
Let him go.
가게 나둬
Let him go!
무모하구만
그건 존경하지
You got stones.
I respect that.
내 생각엔
Tell you what.
네 싸구려 양복하고
월급에 진저리가 나서
You get tired of cheap suits
and government wages,
내게 빌것 같은데
you give me a call.
네가 이겼어
You're above this.
이녀석을 어떻게 잡아야 할까요
So, how we gonna get this guy?
좋은 소식이야
Good news.
밴 혼의 전화기에 도청기를 설치했어
We're clear to wiretap
van Horn's cellphone.
영장은 어떻게 받으셨어요?
How'd you get a warrant?
미국 연방 지방검찰청에 있는
친구에게 연락했지
I got a friend
at the U.S. attorney's office,
딸에게 밴드 캔디를 많이
사줬어야 瑩嗤 말야
and I bought an ungodly amount
of her daughter's band candy.
구하기 힘드셨을텐데요
You can never get enough
band candy.
그래, 힘들었지
No, you can't.
빌어먹을 초콜릿 바만 아니었음
더 쉬웠을텐데 말이야
I just wish
they had something else
besides
those damn chocolate bars.
여네
That's it.
봐바
Behold --
열쇠 복사본이야
A copy of the Suit's key,
네가 가져온 껌틀로 만들었어
fashioned after
your chewing-gum mold.
어떤 금고용인데?
What is it?
네 직감이 맞았어
Well, your instincts
were correct.
래비너사의 10-28 키 조합으로
열리는 벽 금고야
It opens a Rabbiner 10-28
key-lock combination wall safe.
최고 등급이지
Top of the line.
시장에 나온지
몇 달밖에 되지 않은 거잖아
Those have only been
on the market a couple months.
그래, 그 말인 즉슨
Yeah, it means the Suit
공무원씨께서 보안을 강화해야 할
필요성을 느낀거지
recently acquired something
that needs upgraded protection.
미술품 목록?
The art manifest?
기다려봐
The timing works out.
집 안에 숨기고 있는거라면..
If he's hiding it
in his house...
금고를 찾아서 털어야겠지
Find the safe and crack it.
요원님의 집에 침입
해야 하는 거라고
We have to break
into the Burkes'.
좋아, 내가 요원님을 낚고
네가 침입하는건 어때?
Okay, how about I lure
the Burkes out and you break in?
오, 내가 더 힘든 일을 하라고?
Oh, I do the dirty work?
난 항상 웃고있어야 한다고
I have to smile
into their faces.
그게 더 힘들꺼 같은데
That work is plenty dirty,
my friend.
네 추적장치를 걱정해야 하지 않아?
Um, do we have to worry
about your anklet?
아니, 요원님 집은 괜찮아
No, Peter's house is exempted.
알람이 울리지 않을꺼야
It won't trigger an alert.
네 위치를 확인할
빌미만 주지 않는다면
If you don't give him
any reason to check in,
안전할꺼야
we're golden.
닐
Neal...
그 누구도 쉽다고 하지않을꺼야
No one said
this was gonna be easy.
알아, 모즈
I know, Moz.
지금보다 더 좋은 타이밍은 없어
And the timing
couldn't be more perfect.
새라도 더이상 없으니
널 더 붙잡아 둘건 없잖아?
With Sara no longer,
what's keeping you here?
좋아, 금요일은
요원님의 포커 나잇이야
All right, Friday night
is Peter's poker night.
그럼 계획은 금요일로
Let's plan it for Friday.
사모님은 어쩌고?
What about El?
내가 알아서 할게
I'll take care of it.
카프리. 웬일이야
Caffrey.
What are you doing here?
밴 혼에게 도청장치를
설치하셨다면서요
We got the wiretap on van Horn.
그래, 들었어
Yeah, I heard.
이제부턴 시간 싸움이지
So now it's a waiting game.
네, 그럼 기다리는 동안
Yeah, so,
while we were waiting,
술이라도 한잔 할수있을 것 같은데요
I thought maybe you could use
a drink.
들어와
Come on in.
잔 가져올게
I'll get a couple glasses.
네
Okay.
망친것 같아
I screwed up.
네, 조금은요
Aw, a little bit.
당신은 좋은 사람이에요, 존스
But you're a good man, Jones.
- 그래?
- 네
Yeah?
Yeah.
그럼 밴 혼이 그러도록
왜 그냥 나뒀을까?
Then why did I let van Horn
get to me?
제가 징역 4년을 받은것과
같은 이유죠
Mm, same reason that landed me
consecutive
4-year prison sentences.
반사회적인 사람이 원하는걸 얻기위해
잠시 거짓말하는 걸 참는거?
What, an almost sociopathic need
to tell lies of omission
and get something for nothing?
'열정'이라고 말할게요
I was gonna say "passion."
그래, 열정
하지만
Mm. Passion.
But...
네, 그게 세상을 돌아가게하죠
Yeah, it makes
the world go 'round.
원하는걸 가지려는 열정,
가진것을 지키려는 열정
Passion to get what we want,
passion to keep what we have,
잃어버린 걸 돌려받기
위한 열정 말이에요
passion to get back
to things we lost.
그래
No.
난 이유가 있어서 이자벨을 떠났어
I left Isabelle...for a reason.
무슨 이유죠?
Which was?
우리가 같이 있었으면
Which was,
if we had stayed together,
그녀가 힘들었을거야
she would have been miserable.
일도 그만둬야 되고,
항상 이사도 가야돼고
She would've had to quit
her job, move to the city,
사무실에서 내가 얼마나
오래 있어야하는지 잘 알잖아
and you know the hours
that I keep at the Bureau.
서로 볼 시간도 없었을거야
We never would have seen
each other.
그래서 난 결정을 했지
So I made a choice.
떠나기로요?
To leave?
떠나기로
To leave.
모든걸 다 가질 순 없는거지?
We can't have it all, right?
글쎄요, 왜 안되나요?
Well, why not?
- 왜 안되나
Why not?
- 선택엔 희생이 따르기 때문이겠지
- 흠
- Well, because choices are sacrifices.
- Hm.
그리고 그건 필연적으로
And, inevitably,
더 많은걸 얻기 위해선 어떤것을
포기해야 한다는 걸 의미하지
that means giving up
something that you want
for something
that you want more.
그럼, 물어볼게
So, now I have to ask...
닐 카프리에게 "모든 것을 가진다"는게 뭐야?
What does "having it all"
mean to Neal Caffrey?
- 돈 걱정할 필요 없이
- 음
Never having to worry about money.
Hm.
의미 있는 일도 하고
Um, doing something
that's meaningful,
제가 신경쓰고 존경하는 사람들과
같이 지내는 거죠
being surrounded by people
I care about and respect,
you know.
꽤나 꿈 같은 일이죠
That's pretty much the dream.
꺼져
Screw you.
- 꺼지라구요?
- 그래 꺼져
Screw me?
Screw you.
- 넌 이미 꿈을 이뤘잖아
- 오, 왜 그러세요
You're already living the dream.
Oh, come on.
물론 추적장치를 끼고 있지만 말야
Now you are the damned dream
with a tracking anklet.
내가 틀렸나?
Am I wrong?
글쎄요, 꺼지란 말은 다시 돌려줄게요
Well, screw you back, Jones,
저랑 비슷할테니까요
'cause you got
the same things I do.
그래, 뭐
Yeah, well,
아마 비슷하긴 하겠지
maybe not
the same living arrangements.
네
Am I right?
Yeah.
그래도 꽤 괜찮은것 같아
그렇지 않아?
I guess I do have it
pretty good, don't I?
맞아요
Yeah.
우리 둘 다요
Guess we both do.
음
Mm.
누구 오기로 되있나요?
Expecting somebody?
아니
No, I'm not.
혹시 칼리 하는 사람은 아니겠죠?
Is this gonna be somebody else
who knows Kali?
아니길 바라야지
I hope not.
방금 청소를 했으니까
'Cause you just got
the place cleaned up.
아니길 바라야죠
I hope that's not the case.
안녕
Hey.
닐
Neal.
안녕하세요
Hey. How are you?
전 사실 나가려던 참이었거든요
Listen, I was actually
just on my way out,
그럼 좋은 저녁 되세요
so, uh,
you two have a good night.
괜찮은거지?
Hey, is everything okay?
피터 요원님이 무슨 일이 있었는지 말해줬어
Peter told me what happened.
이런 일에 끌어들여서 미안해
I'm sorry
you got dragged into this.
아냐, 그러지마
No, don't be.
덕분에 새 가구도 사고
너도 볼 수 있으니 말야
Gave me a chance
to buy new furniture.
And I got a chance to see you.
8년
Eight years.
주변의 모든 것들이 변했어
Everything around us
has changed.
우리만 빼고 말야
Everything except us.
받아야 돼
I should get that.
전화 받아, 난..
You should get that.
I, uh...
음, 일이야
It's, uh, work.
네, 요원님
Yeah, Peter?
바로 가겠습니다
I'm on my way.
무슨 일이야?
What is it?
배럿-듄에서
Barrett-Dunne.
짐미를 납치했데
They kidnapped Jimmy.
증거를 온 도시에 숨겨놨어
I've planted evidence all over this city.
날 죽이면, 세상에 알려질꺼야
You kill me, it goes public.
살인, 밀수, 모든게 말야
The murder, the smuggling --
All of it.
- 허세 부리는거지
- 한번 시험해볼까?
- You're bluffing.
- You willing to chance it?
어떻게 해서든
Gentlemen, whatever it takes
윌슨이 전부 불게 해둬
to get Mr. Wilson to talk,
do it.
지금 바로 가겠다
I'm on my way in.
기술팀이 한시간 전에 찾아냈다
Our techs picked this up
an hour ago.
어떻게 그를 찾은거죠?
How'd they find him?
30분 전에 도착한 이메일을 찾았어
We intercepted an e-mail chain
a half-hour too late.
짐미는 내부 고발자를
만나는 걸로 알았나보네요
Jimmy thought
he was meeting a whistle-blower.
그리고 밴 혼이 함정에 빠트렸구요
And van Horn set him up.
짐미는 배럿-듄의 건물
어딘가에 있어
Now Jimmy's somewhere
inside Barrett-Dunne.
그곳은 완전 요새에요
The place is a fortress.
총을 든 사람이 한가득일거에요
Lots of men with lots of guns.
어떻게 하죠?
How do we do this?
빠르고 정확하게 해야지
With speed
and precision.
밴 혼은 킬러야
우리가 가는걸 알꺼야
Van Horn's a killer.
He sees us coming --
인질극을 할수도 있어요
Could turn
into a hostage situation.
우리가 가기 전에
짐미를 죽여버릴 수도 있구요
Or he could kill Jimmy
before we get to him.
정당방위라고 하겠죠
Claim it was self-defense.
영장 받기 전에 짐미가
어디있는지 알아낼 수 있다면요?
What if we can figure out
where Jimmy is
before going in with a warrant?
도움이 되겠지
That would help.
Diana, you still have friends
- 다이애나, 아직 국무부에 아는사람 있지?
- 네, 몇 명요
in the State Department, right?
Yeah, a few.
밴 혼과 내일 아침에 약속을
잡도록 할 수 있나?
Powerful enough
to convince van Horn
to take a meeting
first thing tomorrow?
네, 누구랑요?
Sure. Who with?
배럿-듄와 손을 잡으려는
해군 고위 공직자말야
A high-ranking
naval commander
who's looking to do business
with Barrett-Dunne.
제가 들어가서, 짐미가 어디있는지
알아내 볼게요
I poke around, find out
where they're holding Jimmy.
그럼 밴 혼이 움직이려하면
바로 갈 수 있겠지
We move right to him
before van Horn
has a chance to try anything.
할 수 있겠어?
Can you do it?
영국 해군에 있을때
I was an admiral.
해군 제독이었는걸요
Royal Navy.
못들은 걸로 하자
I didn't hear that.
누구도 못들은거야
Nobody heard that.
연필 내려놔
Pencils down.
적지 말고
Don't write that.
어떻게 동작하는지는 알지?
You've got how it works?
손목의 패드를 밴 혼의 보안 카드에
가까이 대면 데이터가 복사되죠
I get van Horn's security-access
card near the wrist pad,
and it clones the data.
배럿-듄의 건물 전체를
통과 할 수 있을거야
Turning it into your very own
Barrett-Dunne all-access pass.
요원님, 제가 팀을 이끌고 싶은데요
Hey, Peter,
I'd like to lead the team in.
안돼. 이번엔 빠져있어
No, you're sitting
this one out.
요원님, 할 수 있습니다
Peter, I can do this.
확신이 서지 않는데
I'm not sure you can.
제가 망쳤어요
I screwed up.
사적인 감정을 끌어들였지만
이번엔 그러지 않을 겁니다
I let things get personal.
It won't happen again.
I --
약속 드릴게요
I promise you that.
보신대로, 제독님. 저희 건물은
저희 장비와 함께
As you've seen, commander,
we're a top-tier facility,
최고의 보안을 자랑합니다
in the equipment
we provide --
훈련된 군사들도 있죠
And in the men you train.
칼리인가요?
Kali?
맞습니다
That's right.
죄송하지만, 일이있어서 가봐야겠네요
안녕히 가십시오
Sorry to run off, but I have business.
You can show yourself out.
짧은 시간에 모든걸
준비해주셔서 감사합니다
I appreciate you fitting me in
on such short notice.
국무부 사람에게 안된다고 할순 없죠
Who am I to say no
to the State Department?
오후에 브리핑 할겁니다
연락 드리죠
I'll be briefing my people this afternoon.
We'll be in touch.
접근 승인
Access granted.
- 들어갔어?
- 네
- Did you get it?
- I did.
8층 엘리베이터 옆에
계단이 하나 있어요
There was a staircase
off the eighth-floor elevator.
밴 혼은 그걸 피했었어요
확인해 볼게요
Van Horn avoided it.
I want to check it out.
조심해
Be careful.
무슨 일이 있으면, 바로 말해
들어갈게
Anything goes sideways,
say the word, and we move in.
밴 혼씨 헬리콥터가 준비 됐습니다
Mr. van Horn,
your helicopter's inbound.
짐미도 옮길 준비 해둬
Get Jimmy ready for transport.
테터보로 공항에 연락해서
(Teterboro : 공항 이름)
Then call Teterboro
요하네스로 갈 사람이 있다고 말해둬
and tell them one passenger
for Johannesburg.
한명 말씀이십니까?
Just the one, sir?
윌슨을 허드슨 밖으로 빼낼꺼야
Mr. Wilson
will be getting out
somewhere over the Hudson.
요원님, 9층에는 무장경비를
제외하곤 아무것도 없어요
Peter, the ninth floor's
completely deserted,
except for an armed guard
outside a room
on the west hallway.
짐미가 있는것 같아?
You think it's Jimmy?
존스?
Jones?
맞을 겁니다
It's got to be him.
블루팀, 건물 안으로
Blue team, move in.
레드팀, 빌딩을 둘러싸고
출구를 봉쇄한다
Red team, surround the building
and watch all exits.
움직여
Let's go.
FBI!
건물에 대한 수색영장이 있습니다
We have a warrant
to search the premises.
흩어져! 지하실을 봉쇄해
Fan out!
Cover the basement!
모든 출구를 확인해!
Check all exits!
사장한테 가서 전해
Tell your men
to stand down.
조종사에게 말해, 난 거의 준비가..
Tell the pilot
that I'm almost --
조심하세요, FBI가 왔습니다
Sir, check your comms.
FBI's on site.
젠장
Damn it.
건물 안팍의 모든 무선기기가
작동하지 않도록 해놔
All right, tell operations
I want every radio transmission
in and out of here jammed.
엘리베이터를 정지 시키고
짐미를 헬리콥터에 태울 시간을 벌어야겠어
Then disable the elevators
and give me time to get Jimmy
to the chopper.
네, 알겠습니다
Yes, sir.
기지 나와라
Eagle to base.
지금 즉시 R6&E 를 정지 시킨다
An immediate R6&E shutdown
per Striker.
알겠습니다
- Roger that, sir.
- What the hell?
907호 밖에 있는 경비녀석에게
더 이상 거기 있을 필요 없다고 해
And inform the guard
outside 907
that he will no longer be needed at his post.
Yes, sir.
사장님?
Sir?
FBI 가 총 소리를 들을수도 있겠지
The FBI might hear gunshots.
하지만 이건 못듣겠지
But they won't hear this.
- 요원님?
- 왜?
Boss?
What?
닐의 시그널이 잡히지 않습니다
Neal's tracer --
signal's out.
닐, 들리나?
Neal, what's your 20?
닐?
Neal?
전파를 방해하고 있습니다
Oh, they're jamming us.
엘리베이터가 작동을 멈췄습니다
The elevators are disabled.
올라 가야겠어요
We got to get up there.
앞장 서. 9층이다
Lead the way.
Ninth floor.
그만 있어도 돼
You're relieved.
사장님 명령이다
Striker's request.
Come on.
네, 알겠습니다
Yes, sir.
방금 경비가 자리를 떴어요
All right, the guard
just left his post.
요원님, 들리나요?
Peter, you copy?
여기 침투하기엔
날을 잘못 잡았구만
Picked a bad day
to break into my world.
살아있는 목표물을 잡는것보다
I got to say,
더 스릴 있는건 없을꺼야
nothing beats the thrill of shooting
at a live target.
움직여 보시지, 제독
Make your move, commander.
이 활이 가까이에서 쏘면
어떻게 되는지 말했던가?
Did I mention what this puppy
can do at close range?
무슨 말인가요?
How about I take your word
for it?
FBI
FBI.
무기 내려놔! 당장!
Lower your weapon.
Now.
움직이지마! 무기를 버려라!
Don't move.
Drop it. Now.
Secure the weapon. Got it?
괜찮아?
Are you okay?
다른 날과 마찬가지죠, 뭐
Just another day.
잘햇어, 존스
Nice work, Jones.
짐미한테 가봐야겠어요
Let's get to Jimmy.
가봐
Go get him.
Secured floor.
짐미, 짐미
괜찮아?
Jimmy.
Jimmy, you good?
내 그림엽서를 받았나 보구나
I take it you got my postcard.
맞아
I did.
나한테 빚진거다
Cost me a flat-screen.
언제 돌아갈꺼야?
When are you headed back?
오늘밤.
한 시간 후에 데리러 올꺼야
Tonight.
Car's picking me up in an hour.
버틸만 해?
How you holding up?
"작은 죄를 인정하다"랑
I'm using phrases
like "copped a plea."
"밀수 공모를 저지르다"가
오늘 떠올랐어
Oh, and "conspiracy to commit
smuggling" popped up today.
그건, 새로운 거지
That's --
that's a new one.
음, 짐미가 밴 혼을 잡는걸 도와줬으니
Well, Jimmy got out
before the murder,
and he helped us
take down van Horn,
형량을 감면 받을 수 있을꺼야
so we should be able to get him
a reduced sentence.
어떻게 될지도 모르고
뛰어들었으니 어쩔 수 없지
Well, he jumped into something
without considering
the consequences.
아마 괜찮을꺼야
Happens to the best of us.
둘이 다시 만나는거야?
You two gonna make it?
그는 형량을 살아야 할테고
난 그걸 도와 주겠지
He'll do time,
and I'll help him through it.
그러고 나면 다시 돌아가겠지
After that, we'll see.
운 좋은 녀석이야
He's a lucky guy.
너도
You're pretty lucky yourself.
이제 가봐야..
I should probably...
그래
Yeah.
햄 좀 가져왔어
I got some deviled ham.
오
Oh.
무슨 일 있어요?
What's going on?
우리의 용의자께서 오늘 저녁에
움직일 모양인가봐
Our repo trader
might be making his move
tonight.
닐은 또 잠복한다고 불평하고있고
And Neal's complaining
about another stakeout.
아뇨, 아뇨
불평하는게 아니라
Oh, no, no.
I'm not complaining.
사실을 말하는것 뿐이에요
I'm stating a fact.
잠복을 또 하느니, 차라리
제 손을 망치로 찍는게 낫겠어요
I would rather pound my thumb
with a hammer
than do another stakeout.
내가 할게
I'll do it.
- 망치로 내리찍는다고?
- 아니 잠복근무 말야
What, pound his thumb?
No, do the stakeout.
- 정말? 괜찮겠어?
- 네
- Really? You don't mind?
- No.
네, 괜찮아요
Not at all.
사실
As a matter of fact,
좀 그립기도 하구요
uh, kind of miss it.
고마워요, 고마워요
존스
Thank you.
Thank you, Jones.
포커하러 안 오실거에요?
You sure you want to miss
poker night?
그래, 괜찮아
Yeah, I don't mind.
난 밤샘 작업도 즐기거든
I kind of enjoy
these all-nighters,
뭐 누군가는 불평을 하기도 하지만말야
whereas some choose
to complain about it.
제가 밴에 들어가면 어떤지 아시잖아요
불안해 진다구요
You know how I get in the van.
I get anxious.
잘 알지, 그래, 알고말고
I sweat.
I do know. I do know.
좋은 저녁 보내
You have a good night.
요원님도요
You too.
모즈, 아마 요원님은 밤새 밴에
있을꺼야
Hey, Moz, Peter's pulling
an all-nighter in the van.
완벽해
Perfect.
지금 공무원씨 집으로 가는 길이야
I'm en route to the
Suit family estate right now.
내키지는 않지만, 꼭 해야돼
We don't have to like it,
but it has to be done.
그래, 알아
Yeah. I know.
행운을 빈다
눈깜짝 할 사이에 해결해
Good luck, my friend.
Godspeed.
그럼, 우리 전시회랑 저녁이있네
Well, so, we have
an art exhibit and dinner.
뭐 부터 할지 정해봐
I think you pulled a fast one.
제가요?
Moi?
얼른
Come on.
로랑? 보려면 몇달은 걸릴텐데
Laurent?
Takes months to get in there.
아무것도 아니에요
Oh, it's nothing.
누가 협박한지 다 알아요
I know a guy
who blackmailed a guy.
스판덱스에 관한건데
물어보진 않았어요
Something about spandex.
I don't ask questions.
날 생각해주는건
정말 의미깊은데 말야
Well, it means a lot to me
that you thought of me,
고마워
so thank you.
뭘요
No, really.
그건 스판덱스였어요
It was, uh, spandex.
좋아
All right.
좋아.
사치, 얌전히 있어야돼
Okay.
Satch, you be good.
- 넌 있어야돼
- 시간이 없어요
You stay.
No, no, chop-chop.
- 늦겠어요
- 그래, 그래
Okay.
Don't want to be late.
Okay, okay.
Here you go.
그렇게 보지마
Don't look at me like that.
요원님, 잠복 근무는 어때요?
Hey, Peter, how's the stakeout?
존스가 커피 사러 갔어
Jones is on a coffee run.
사무실 나가기 전에 했던
전화 말인데..
Listen, that call you made
before you left the office
tonight...
네?
Yeah?
새라였어?
Was it Sara?
아니요, 제 전화 안받고 있어요
She hasn't been taking
my calls.
이런
Aw, man.
신경 쓰이겠네
That's got to be weighing
on you.
네
You have no idea.
들어봐, 우린 이때까지
여러 일을 해냈고
Listen...You and I have been
through some stuff,
물론 서로 거리를 두고 있지만
and we've had to keep things
from each other.
얘기하고 싶은게 있으면
But...if you want to talk,
그러니까,
진지하게 얘기하는것 말야
and I --
you know, I mean, really talk...
언제든지 말해
I'm here for you.
밴 안이 심심해서 그러시는 거죠?
Is this the loneliness
of the van talking?
아마도
Maybe, maybe.
하지만, 음..
But, uh, I --
넌 이제 행복해져도 돼
you know, I think
you deserve some happiness.
그리고, 난..
And I, uh --
내가 도와 줄 수 있는게 있으면 알려줘
whatever I can do
to help you with that...
Let me know.
고마워요, 요원님
Thanks, Peter.
힘이 되네요
That means a lot.
그래
Yeah.
천만에
No problem.
내일 보자, 닐
See you tomorrow, Neal.
내일 뵈요
See you tomorrow.
모즈
Hey.
긴장감 때문에 죽을지경이야
The suspense is killing me.
금고는 찾았어?
Did you find the safe?
응
I did.
열었어?
Did you get in?
응
I did.
그리고?
And?
미술품 목록은 없었어, 모즈
The manifest
wasn't in there, Moz.
미안해
I'm sorry.
너도 이 일이 쉬운게 아니라는 걸 알잖아
Listen, we both knew
this was a long shot, right?
알아, 하지만
Well, yes, but I --
나가야겠다, 내일 얘기하자
Listen, I got to get out of here.
Let's talk tomorrow.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com